<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="description_adaptive_brightness_tile">「自動亮度模式」開啟時會令手機根據現場周圍環境光亮情況而自動調節屏幕亮度，開啟後你仍然可以手動調節屏幕亮度。\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予修改系統設定的權限。(https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SETTINGS)</string>
    <string name="description_alarm_tile">「鬧鐘」主要提供「顯示下一個鬧鐘」及「新增鬧鐘」 兩個選項。如已有設定的鬧鐘時間，快速設定磚將會顯示下一個鬧鐘時間。除了內置原生的時鐘程式，此快速設定磚亦能支援其他第三方時鐘應用程式。</string>
    <string name="description_ambient_display_tile">「環境顯示」開啟後會在裝置收到通知時短暫在鎖定屏幕顯示通知供快速查閱。\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予可寫入安全設定的權限。(https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS)</string>
    <string name="description_animations_tile">「動畫」允許變更視窗動畫比例、轉場動畫比例及Animator片長比例。\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予可寫入安全設定的權限。(https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS)</string>
    <string name="description_application_tile">「應用程式」允許建立包含多個應用程式清單或選取單一應用程式並快速存取。</string>
    <string name="description_awake_while_plugged_in_tile">「充電時保持亮屏」開啟時會令裝置在充電時一直保持亮屏狀態。\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予可寫入安全設定的權限。(https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS)</string>
    <string name="description_battery_saver_tile">「省電模式」允許快速開啟或關閉省電模式。節約電池用量模式開啟後有助於延長電池壽命，但會降低裝置的效能。並限制震動、定位服務和大部分的背景資料。\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予可寫入安全設定的權限。 (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS)</string>
    <string name="description_brightness_tile">「亮度」允許快速設定亮度程度(高、中、低）\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予修改系統設定的權限。 (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SETTINGS)</string>
    <string name="description_calculator_tile">「計算機」，如有安裝Google的計算機，快速設定磚將會開啟應用程式。</string>
    <string name="description_calendar_tile">「日曆」提供「開啟日曆活動內容」或「新增活動」，此快速設定磚亦能支援其他第三方日曆應用程式。</string>
    <string name="description_call_tile">「電話」提供「選取指定聯絡人號碼並進行快速撥號」或「開啟電話應用程式」。此快速設定磚亦能支援其他第三方電話應用程式。\n使用此快速設定磚需要需要獲取電話通話及撥號的權限才能使用。詳情可參閱(https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#CALL_PHONE)</string>
    <string name="description_camera_tile">「相機」，利用快速設定磚直接打開相機應用程式的「相片拍攝」或「影片拍攝」模式。此快速設定磚亦能支援其他第三方相機應用程式。</string>
    <string name="description_clipboard_tile">「剪貼板」，可查看剪貼板最新的內容，並可以進行複製、分享或儲存至其他應用程式。</string>
    <string name="description_data_roaming_tile">「數據漫遊」，快速開啟或關閉數據漫遊。\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予可寫入安全設定的權限。 (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS)</string>
    <string name="description_demo_mode_tile">「示範模式」，允許開啟及進入Android內建的示範模式，並允許使用者對示範模式進行設定，例如狀態列等。用戶可利用「示範模式」配合一些屏幕截圖或演示需要。\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予可寫入安全設定的權限及檢測系統資訊的權限。 (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS)； (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#DUMP) </string>
    <string name="description_density_tile">Change the density of the screen.</string>
    <string name="description_email_tile">Choose a contact to quickly email or launch the email app. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to compose and send emails.</string>
    <string name="description_files_tile">Launch Android\'s built-in file manager to explore the storage of the device.</string>
    <string name="description_font_size_tile">Change the font size the device shows.\nModify system settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SETTINGS) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_heads_up_notifications_tile">Some notifications may appear in a small floating window when the device is active. Turn it off to avoid disturbances; especially helpful for when watching a video or playing a game.\nWrite secure settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_immersive_mode_tile">Hide the status bar, the navigation bar or both for a truly full screen interface system wide.\nWrite secure settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_keep_tile">Open a dialog to add a new note in Google\'s proprietary Keep app, if installed. </string>
    <string name="description_location_tile">Turn location mode on or off or change location accuracy.\nHigh accuracy mode uses GPS, Wi-Fi, cellular networks, and other sensors to get the highest-accuracy location for the device. It uses Google\'s location service to help estimate the location of the device faster and more accurately.\nBattery saving mode estimates the location of the device using low battery-intensive location sources, like Wi-Fi and cellular networks. It uses Google\'s location service to help estimate the location of the device faster and more accurately.\nDevice only mode estimates the location of the device using GPS only. It doesn\'t use Google\'s location service to provide location information. This mode may use more battery power and take longer to determine the location of the device.\nWrite secure settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_lock_tile">Securely lock the device. If a screen lock (password, PIN, pattern, …) is set, please follow the provided unlocking procedure to unlock the device. Device administrator must be activated.</string>
    <string name="description_maps_tile">Launch Google\'s proprietary Maps app, if installed, showing the current location of the device. This tile makes use of the Google Awareness API (https://developers.google.com/awareness).\nLocation permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#ACCESS_FINE_LOCATION) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_multi_window_tile">Android Nougat adds support to display more than one app at the same time: two apps can run side-by-side or one above the other in split-screen mode. The accessibility service must be enabled.</string>
    <string name="description_nfc_tile">Turn NFC on or off, or open NFC settings. \nWrite secure settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS) is required to change NFC state.</string>
    <string name="description_orientation_lock_tile">Lock the orientation of the device: 0\u00B0, 90\u00B0, 180\u00B0, 270\u00B0. To change and lock orientation, the tile needs to turn auto-rotate off.\nModify system settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SETTINGS) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_power_tile">Show a dialog to power off, reboot, reboot recovery, reboot bootloader. To show the system power dialog, the accessibility service must be enabled.</string>
    <string name="description_power_dialog_accessibility_tile">Show the Android system power dialog to power off or restart the device. The accessibility service must be enabled.</string>
    <string name="description_recents_screen_tile">Show the recents screen, a system-level UI that lists recently accessed activities and tasks. The accessibility service must be enabled.</string>
    <string name="description_reminder_tile">Quickly add a reminder to be shown as a persistent notification. Edit or delete the reminder by tapping the notification.</string>
    <string name="description_ringer_mode_tile">Set the ringer mode of the device: normal, vibrate or Do Not Disturb. Do Not Disturb access is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_screen_on_tile">Keep the device awake overriding the sleep timeout setting. To let the device go back to sleep, stop the service or turn the screen off.</string>
    <string name="description_screenshot_tile">Take a screenshot of the device.\nWrite external storage permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_settings_shortcut_tile">Open Android\'s hidden or hard-to-find settings.</string>
    <string name="description_sleep_tile">Put the device to sleep.</string>
    <string name="description_sleep_time_tile">Take a look at the time the device has spent sleeping, with details about the capacity of the battery and the charging state.</string>
    <string name="description_sleep_timeout_tile">Change how long it takes for the device to go to sleep when inactive.\nModify system settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SETTINGS) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_street_view_tile">Launch Google\'s proprietary Street View app, if installed, showing the current location of the device. This tile makes use of the Google Awareness API (https://developers.google.com/awareness).\nLocation permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#ACCESS_FINE_LOCATION) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_sync_tile">Turn sync on or off, or open sync settings.</string>
    <string name="description_text_tile">Open a dialog to write anything, to copy, to share, or to save with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to share text.</string>
    <string name="description_timer_tile">Start a countdown timer. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to start a countdown timer.</string>
    <string name="description_touch_sounds_tile">Turn touch sounds on or off.\nModify system settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SETTINGS) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_vibrate_for_calls_tile">Turn vibrations for incoming calls on or off.\nModify system settings permission (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SETTINGS) is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_vibrate_on_tap_tile">「開觸控震動」允許快速開啟或關閉觸控震動。\n使用此快速設定磚需要授予修改系統設定的權限。 (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#WRITE_SETTINGS)</string>
    <string name="description_voice_tile">「語音」，利用語音控制裝置或其他支援的操作。</string>
    <string name="description_volumes_tile">「音量」，開啟音量面板並調校各項音量包括鬧鐘、媒體、鈴聲及通話音量。需要獲取「請勿打擾」模式的權限才能使用。</string>
    <string name="description_weather_tile">「天氣」，開啟視窗顯示現時的天氣情況，例如溫度、體感感度、濕度、露點等。此設定磚採用Google的情境感知API（Google Awareness API）進行開發，詳情可參閱 (https://developers.google.com/awareness)。\n並需要獲取位置權限才能使用，詳情可參閱(https://developer.android.com/reference/android/Manifest.permission.html#ACCESS_FINE_LOCATION)</string>
    <string name="description_web_search_tile">「網絡搜尋」，進行網絡搜尋，亦可配合支援網絡搜尋操作的第三方應用程式使用。</string>
</resources>
