<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="description_activities_tile">アプリの隠れたアクティビティを起動するタイルを５つまで追加できます。</string>
    <string name="description_adaptive_brightness_tile">有効にすると、周囲に合わせて明るさを最適化します。明るさの自動調整を有効にしても明るさを調整することができます。\nこのタイルを使用するにはシステム設定の書き込みの許可が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_alarm_tile">現在設定されているアラームを表示、または新しくアラームを設定します。アラームが設定されている場合、次のアラームをタイルに表示します。このアクションはアラームの表示と編集のために、Androidの既定のブロードキャストを受け取れるサードパーティ製のアプリとの互換性があります。</string>
    <string name="description_ambient_display_tile">通知を受け取った時にロック画面の内容を端末に表示します。\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_animations_tile">アニメーター再生時間とトランジションアニメとウィンドウアニメのスケールを設定します。\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_application_tile">ダイアログに表示するアプリのリストを作成します。\n単一のアプリのタイルも5つまで利用できます。</string>
    <string name="description_awake_while_plugged_in_tile">充電中に画面をスリープにしません。\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_battery_details_tile">Show a persistent notification with details about the battery of the device: percentage, charging and discharging state, health, temperature, voltage and technology. The label and the icon of the tile display the percentage of the battery when the notification is active.</string>
    <string name="description_battery_saver_tile">Turn battery saver on and off. While battery saver is on, performance is reduced and location services and background data are turned off.\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_bluetooth_tile">Turn bluetooth on or off, or open bluetooth settings.</string>
    <string name="description_brightness_tile">Set three different levels (high, medium &amp; low) of brightness to cycle through.\nModify system settings permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_caffeine_tile">Keep the device awake overriding the sleep timeout setting. To let the device go back to sleep, stop the service or turn the screen off.</string>
    <string name="description_calculator_tile">Launch Google\'s proprietary Calculator app, if installed.</string>
    <string name="description_calendar_tile">Show calendar\'s events or add a new one. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to show and add calendar events.</string>
    <string name="description_call_tile">Choose a contact\'s number to quickly dial or launch the phone app. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to initiate a phone call.\nPhone call permission is required to initiate a phone call directly from the tile without going through the dialer user interface.</string>
    <string name="description_camera_tile">Launch the camera app in photo or video mode. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to launch the camera in photo and video mode.</string>
    <string name="description_camera_lock_tile">Prevent use of all device cameras. Device administrator must be activated.</string>
    <string name="description_cellular_data_tile">Open mobile network settings or data usage settings, if available. On devices with super user privileges turn cellular data on or off.</string>
    <string name="description_clipboard_tile">View the content of the latest clipping, to copy, to share, or to save with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to share text.</string>
    <string name="description_contacts_tile">Quickly access the details of the selected contact to call, text, edit, …</string>
    <string name="description_counter_tile">A simple counter.</string>
    <string name="description_data_roaming_tile">Turn data roaming on or off.\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_demo_mode_tile">Enter Android Demo mode. Demo mode allows the device to force the status bar into a fixed state, useful for taking screenshots with a consistent status bar state, or with testing different status icon permutations.\nWrite secure settings permission and dump permission are required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_density_tile">Change the density of the screen.</string>
    <string name="description_email_tile">Choose a contact to quickly email or launch the email app. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to compose and send emails.</string>
    <string name="description_font_size_tile">Change the font size the device shows.\nModify system settings permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_heads_up_notifications_tile">Some notifications may appear in a small floating window when the device is active. Turn it off to avoid disturbances; especially helpful for when watching a video or playing a game.\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_immersive_mode_tile">Hide the status bar, the navigation bar or both for a truly full screen interface system wide.\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_input_method_tile">Show input method picker or open input method settings.</string>
    <string name="description_invert_colors_tile">Simulate colors inversion.\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_keep_tile">Open a dialog to add a new note in Google\'s proprietary Keep app, if installed.</string>
    <string name="description_location_tile">Turn location mode on or off or change location accuracy.\nHigh accuracy mode uses GPS, Wi-Fi, cellular networks, and other sensors to get the highest-accuracy location for the device. It uses Google\'s location service to help estimate the location of the device faster and more accurately.\nBattery saving mode estimates the location of the device using low battery-intensive location sources, like Wi-Fi and cellular networks. It uses Google\'s location service to help estimate the location of the device faster and more accurately.\nDevice only mode estimates the location of the device using GPS only. It doesn\u2019t use Google\'s location service to provide location information. This mode may use more battery power and take longer to determine the location of the device.\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_lock_tile">Securely lock the device. If a screen lock (password, PIN, pattern, …) is set, please follow the provided unlocking procedure to unlock the device. Device administrator must be activated.</string>
    <string name="description_maps_tile">Launch any maps application, if installed, showing the current location of the device. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to decode geolocation parameters. This tile makes use of the Google Awareness API.\nLocation permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_media_volume_tile">Change the mute state of the volume of audio streams for multimedia playback.</string>
    <string name="description_memory_tile">Show a persistent notification with details about the memory of the device: available, used, threshold, low memory. The label of the tile displays the available memory of the device when the notification is active.</string>
    <string name="description_mono_audio_tile">音声再生時のチャンネルを統合します".</string>
    <string name="description_monochromacy_tile">画面をモノクロ (白黒) 表示にします。\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_multi_window_tile">Android Nougat以降では分割画面がサポートされています。： 2つのアプリを上下/左右に並べて表示できます。このタイルを利用するには、ユーザー補助サービスを有効にする必要があります。</string>
    <string name="description_nfc_tile">Turn NFC on or off, or open NFC settings.\nWrite secure settings permission is required to change NFC state.</string>
    <string name="description_notification_light_tile">通知LEDのを切り替えます。</string>
    <string name="description_orientation_lock_tile">Lock the orientation of the device: 0\u00B0, 90\u00B0, 180\u00B0, 270\u00B0. To change and lock orientation, the tile needs to turn auto-rotate off.\nModify system settings permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_power_tile">Show a dialog to power off, reboot, reboot recovery, reboot bootloader. To show the system power dialog, the accessibility service must be enabled.</string>
    <string name="description_power_dialog_accessibility_tile">Show the Android system power dialog to power off or restart the device. The accessibility service must be enabled.</string>
    <string name="description_recents_screen_tile">Show the recents screen, a system-level UI that lists recently accessed activities and tasks. The accessibility service must be enabled.</string>
    <string name="description_reminder_tile">Quickly add a reminder to be shown as a persistent notification. Edit or delete the reminder by tapping the notification.</string>
    <string name="description_ringer_mode_tile">Set the ringer mode of the device: normal, vibrate or Do Not Disturb. Do Not Disturb access is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_screenshot_tile">Take a screenshot of the device.\nWrite external storage permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_settings_shortcut_tile">Open Android\'s hidden or hard-to-find settings.</string>
    <string name="description_shortcuts_tile">Choose and set shortcuts to perform specific actions within any application that implements such feature.\nPhone call permission is required to perform direct dial shortcuts.</string>
    <string name="description_sleep_tile">端末をスリープします。</string>
    <string name="description_sleep_timeout_tile">Change how long it takes for the device to go to sleep when inactive.\nModify system settings is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_stopwatch_tile">Show a dialog with a stopwatch.</string>
    <string name="description_storage_tile">Open storage settings or launch Android\'s built-in file manager to explore the storage of the device.</string>
    <string name="description_street_view_tile">Launch Google\'s proprietary Street View app, if installed, showing the current location of the device. This tile makes use of the Google Awareness API.\nLocation permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_sync_tile">同期を切り替えるか、同期の設定を開きます。</string>
    <string name="description_text_tile">Open a dialog to write anything, to copy, to share, or to save with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to share text.</string>
    <string name="description_timer_tile">Start a countdown timer. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to start a countdown timer.</string>
    <string name="description_touch_sounds_tile">Turn touch sounds on or off.\nModify system settings permissions required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_up_time_tile">Show a persistent notification with the up time of the device. The label of the tile displays the up time of the device when the notification is active.</string>
    <string name="description_usb_debugging_tile">Turn debug mode when USB is connected on or off.\nこのタイルを使用するにはWRITE_SECURE_SETTINGSの権限が必要です。</string>
    <string name="description_vibrate_for_calls_tile">Turn vibrations for incoming calls on or off.\nModify system settings permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_vibrate_on_tap_tile">Turn vibrations for taps on or off.\nModify system settings permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_voice_tile">Use voice actions to control the device or perform supported actions.</string>
    <string name="description_volumes_tile">Control the volume streams of the device: alarm, media, ring and call (on voice capable devices). Do Not Disturb access is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_vpn_tile">Show settings to allow configuration of VPN.</string>
    <string name="description_weather_tile">Open a dialog with the current weather conditions, temperature, feels like, humidity and dew point. This tile makes use of the Google Awareness API.\nLocation permission is required to use this tile.</string>
    <string name="description_web_search_tile">Start a web search. The action is compatible with third-party apps that can receive the Android default broadcast to initiate a web search.</string>
</resources>
